const questionsLimit=10;


const quiz = [
    {
        question: "She ____ in the garden all morning.",
        answer: "has been cooking",
        choices: [ "has cooked",  "has been cooking",  "cooked",  "was cooking"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ for the exam since last week.",
        answer: "studied",
        choices: [ "has studied",  "has been studying",  "studied",  "was studying"]
    },

    {
        question: "They ____ in the marathon for two hours.",
        answer: "have been running",
        choices: [ "have run",  "have been running",  "ran",  "were running"]
    },

    {
        question: "I ____ on this project all day.",
        answer: "have been working",
        choices: [ "have worked",  "have been working",  "worked",  "was working"]
    },

    {
        question: "She ____ at the computer since 9 AM.",
        answer: "sat" ,
        choices: [ "has sat",  "has been sitting",  "sat",  "was sitting"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ with his friends for two hours.",
        answer: "has been playing",
        choices: [ "has played",  "has been playing",  "played",  "was playing"]
    },

    {
        question: "The kids ____ in the pool all afternoon.",
        answer: "have been swimming",
        choices: [ "have swum",  "have been swimming",  "swam",  "were swimming"]
    },

    {
        question: "I ____ for the bus for 30 minutes.",
        answer: "have been waiting",
        choices: [ "have waited",  "have been waiting",  "waited",  "was waiting"]
    },

    {
        question: "They ____ on the project since last month.",
        answer: "have been working",
        choices: [ "have worked",  "have been working",  "worked",  "were working"]
    },

    {
        question: "She ____ her guitar for an hour.",
        answer: "has been playing",
        choices: [ "has played",  "has been playing",  "played",  "was playing"]
    },

    {
        question: "The students ____ the test for  hours."
        , answer: "have been taking",
        choices: [ "have taken",  "have been taking",  "took",  "were taking"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ his phone all day.",
        answer: "has been checking",
        choices: [ "has checked",  "has been checking",  "checked",  "was checking"]
    },

    {
        question: "She ____ the house for two hours.",
        answer: "has been cleaning",
        choices: [ "has cleaned",  "has been cleaning",  "cleaned",  "was cleaning"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ the guitar for an hour.",
        answer: "has been playing",
        choices: [ "has played",  "has been playing",  "played",  "was playing"]
    },

    {
        question: "I ____ for this moment all my life.",
        answer: "have been waiting",
        choices: [ "have waited",  "have been waiting",  "waited",  "was waiting"]
    },

    {
        question: "They ____ the project since last month.",
        answer: "have been working",
        choices: [ "have worked",  "have been working",  "worked",  "were working"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ to music for hours.",
        answer: "has been listening",
        choices: [ "has listened",  "has been listening",  "listened",  "was listening"]
    },

    {
        question: "The kids ____ in the pool all afternoon.",
        answer:  "have been swimming",
        choices: [ "have swum",  "have been swimming",  "swam",  "were swimming"]
    },

    

    {
        question: "They ____ the project since last month."
        , answer: "have been working",
        choices: [ "have worked",  "have been working",  "worked",  "were working"]
    },

    {
        question: "He ____ to music for hours.",
        answer: "has been listening",
        choices: [ "has listened",  "has been listening",  "listened",  "was listening"]
    },

    {
        question: "The kids ____ in the pool all afternoon.",
        answer:  "have been swimming",
        choices: [ "have swum",  "have been swimming",  "swam",  "were swimming"]
    },




























]